It's really sweat what Howard
wants to do for Bernadette.
(Penny:)Yeah. Hey, how come
you've never done anything romantic
to celebrate our fist date?
(Leonard:)Well, for starters, you've broken up
with me so many times,
(Leonard:)which first date
are we talking about?
Whoa! Somebody call
the burn ward.
(Sheldon:)And back to the zone.
(Leonard:)And besides, I do romantic things
for you all the time.
(Leonard:)Can you even name one romantic thing
you've done for me?
(Penny:)-I can name tons.
-Sex doesn't count.
(Penny:)I know, what about
that bed-and-breakfast?
(Leonard:)Well, I took you there.
All you did was...
(Penny:)I know what I did.
(Penny:)I bet they had to throw out
that rocking chair.
(Penny:)You know, I can be romantic
if I want to.
(Leonard:)It's fine. And also not true.
Okay, just you wait and sea.
(Penny:)I'm gonna romance
your freakin' ass off.
(Leonard:)That's beautiful.
Is that Shakespeare?